When they find out
how you're treating
the best coach in
the fucking league...
Sir, sir, sir,
sir, please,
please,
I'm begging
you, please.
Let him go.
Get fuck off me.
This is
all your fault.
If it weren't for
you, I still have
one hell of a coach!
Sir,
do you really think
he won that game
on skill alone?
What are
you getting at?
Ted was
my assistant,
he knows my
whole playbook.
How else could he
have beaten me?
That bastard.
No wonder he
turned down my offer.
Sir,
you still
own the Giants.
They're headed to
the Super Bowl.
If you give me
another shot,
I'll demolish him.
And if you lose?
Scrub stadium toilets
for the rest
of my life.
I'll talk to
the commissioner
about West.
Are you seriously
trying to bribe me
after what he did?
We're taking him out.
I'm an official
of this league
and I take it
very responsibly.
I'm not just going
to sit around here
and let people...
thank you so much.
I hope you
have a good day.
This is like a
signing bonus
for the...
You're lucky
you don't get fired.
That's fair.
I'm bringing
you to the Giants
as an assistant.
Don't worry, sir.
He's gonna
regret everything
he's ever done.
Yeah, he damn
well better.